company-director-check.co.uk 2011-12-27

# Director Check - find free company director information

  | 

Company Director Check are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from you. Please read the following to understand our practices regarding personal information and how they affect you as you use our features and services. 

This statement discloses our current privacy practices as at 15th September 2011.

This Privacy Statement answers the following questions:

  * What information does Company Director Check gather about you? 
  * How does Company Director Check use your personal information? 
  * How do we use "IP addresses" and "cookies"? 
  * Will Company Director Check disclose any of your personal information? 
  * What kind of security measures do we take to protect your information from accidental loss or disclosure? 
  * Will Company Director Check use your information for direct mailings? 
  * How can you deactivate your account or correct or revise information that we have about you? 
  * How do we respect children's privacy? 
  * What else should you know about your privacy? 
  * How will you know whether Company Director Check's privacy policy has changed? 

### What Information Does Company Director Check Gather About You?

Company Director Check collects information about our visitors so that we can provide a more interesting and useful service, as well as more appropriate advertising. We ask for your name, email address, and other personal information when you register to use certain features of our website, or if you sign up for special or personalized services, such as our monitor emails. We also may ask for this information at other times, such as when you enter contests or other promotions sponsored by our partners. 

If you use our recommendation service to email one of our pages to a friend, you will need to provide us with your friend's email address. We will automatically send this person a one-time email, with the recommended URL attached, as well as invite your friend to visit and register with our site. We will not use these email addresses for any other purpose.

We collect IP addresses for site security and to help us understand how people use our sites so that we can improve our sites and our users' respective experiences. For similar quality reasons, we use a feature known as a "cookie." Cookies contain bits of information that websites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more convenient by storing information about your preferences on a site. Although we may assign your browser a cookie, the cookie does not tell us who you are. Only you can tell us that. 

When you place an order for a product or service, we need to know the sort of information typically used for credit card transactions, such as your name, mailing and billing addresses, telephone number, and credit card number and expiration date. Gathering this information allows us to process and fulfill your order and notify you of your order status. We use Google Checkout and PayPay UK to handle all our transactions.

If you enter companies into a Monitor or Alert system, we will save that information, and use it to identify content that we think is relevant to you. We will also use that information in the aggregate to help us better understand what our community and our premium members are interested in, so we can create and target our content better.

We may also collect your email address when you submit content to our sites (for example, a contest entry, or a review of a product). Unless we get your approval, we will not display your address with your submission.

Besides cookies, we may also use tiny electronic images (called "single-pixel GIFs" or "Web beacons"), which allow us to count users who have visited specific pages or access certain cookies. We may use single-pixel GIFs in the following ways:

  * To count and recognize users. 
  * To conduct research on behalf of some partners on their websites, and for auditing purposes. 
  * To determine aggregate information about users, including demographic and usage information. 
  * To determine which email messages were opened and/or acted upon when we send HTML-formatted email messages (messages resembling Web pages that include graphics). 

Advertising networks that serve ads on our site may also use single-pixel GIFs in their advertisements. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a Web page, including an ad banner, can act as a Web beacon.

### How Does Company Director Check Use Your Personal Information?

Company Director Check collects personal information to provide you, the user, with the best and most personalized experience possible, and to provide our advertisers with an efficient way to reach the right audience. In short, by knowing a little about you, Company Director Check can deliver more relevant content and advertisements to you.

We conduct research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based upon the information you provide us when you register or participate in contests or other promotions on our site, or based upon the information on our server log files. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. We may also notify you of products, services, or areas of our site that we think may interest you based on the information we've received.

In addition to helping us process your order, we use the information we collect from you when you buy a product or service from us so that we can provide you with an enhanced, more personalized shopping experience. We will also send you occasional discount alerts and notices about products and services that we think may interest you.

Sometimes we ask for personal information when providing special features and services. You do not have to give us that information, but without it, you may not be able to take advantage of those products or services. For example, you will be unable to track your search history on our site and you may not be able to gain access to certain areas of our site unless you register and/or subscribe.

### How Do We Use "IP Addresses" and "Cookies"?

#### IP Addresses

Your Web browser or email application automatically provides your Internet Protocol address ("IP address") to other computers with which you communicate over the Internet, so that they know where to send you information.

We receive an IP address each time you view one of our Web pages, because the browser automatically reports it to us. We also may store the IP address when you register with Company Director Check.

We may use IP addresses for various purposes, including:

  * Diagnosing service or technology problems. 
  * Assessing and maintaining system security. 
  * Displaying the most appropriate advertising or content. 
  * Studying how people use our site and how we can improve it. 
  * Reporting to advertisers about aggregate, but not individual, information derived from IP addresses. 

#### Cookies

Cookies are used on our sites in the following ways:

  * We use cookies to access your stored account information automatically when you log on to our site, in order to deliver a better and more personalized service. 
  * We use cookies to estimate our audience size and usage patterns. The unique cookie that is given to each browser accessing Company Director Check is then used to determine usage patterns and help us target content and ads based upon user interests. 
  * We use cookies to allow you to access your account information automatically, as well as make changes to your personal information. 
  * Our search engines may use cookies to expedite your search for content or products.

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can configure yours to refuse cookies or notify you when you've received one. Browsers differ, so check your "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you reject cookies on our sites, though, you will not be able to access all areas of them or use many of their features, including our discussion boards and portfolio tracker. When you accept our cookies, we cannot use them to find out who you really are, unless you tell us.

### Will Company Director Check Disclose Any of Your Personal Information?

Company Director Check will not disclose any personally identifiable information about individual users, except as described in this Privacy Statement. With the few exceptions that we explain here, we do not give, rent, lend, or sell individual information to anyone outside our company, although we do provide aggregate information. For example, we might tell an advertiser that there are 30,000 users monitoring companies in London, but we will not tell them that you are one of them, nor will we tell them that your email address is cleverboy@gettingbetterinfo.com. We may also use this aggregated information to help the advertisers reach the kind of audience they want. They may give us an ad and tell us the type of audience they want to reach. Company Director Check (or people working on our behalf, under contracts and confidentiality agreements) would then take the ad and display it to users who have told us they meet those criteria. We may also disclose aggregate information (for example, information showing that 50,000 of our visitors clicked on a particular advertising banner last month) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

As for individually identifiable information, we may disclose it only under the following circumstances:

  * We may disclose information to others when we have your consent. 
  * If you sign up for a service that relies upon third parties for important elements, we will provide your personal information to the third parties so that they can provide you with their services, and those companies will treat the data under their own policies. We will tell you about these service providers at the time you sign up for the service. 
  * If you buy something from us, we will disclose your personal information to the extent necessary to fulfill your order and charge your credit card (if applicable).
  * If you use our recommendation service to email one of our articles to a friend, Company Director Check will automatically send this person a one-time email, with the recommended URL attached. The email address you give us will appear on the "From" line of the email, thereby disclosing this information to whoever opens and reads the email. Similarly, if you send email from our site, by using "Reply to Author" or "Email this Post," your address may appear as the return address of that email. 
  * We may disclose your personal information as required by applicable law, or in response to legal process, to protect the rights or property of Company Director Check, or to protect the safety of Company Director Check, our users, or others. 
  * We may sometimes conduct mailings to other people's lists. So we may cross reference our user lists to prevent duplication and spam.
  * We may disclose personal information in some other limited circumstances, but we will specifically describe them to you when we collect the information, such as in the rules of a contest or a new service. For example, if we are going to give personal information to a contest's sponsor, we will disclose it when you sign up for the contest, so that you can decide whether to enter. 
  * We may employ contractors or other third parties to help with our operations. We may give them access to databases of user information, so that they can perform their services for us, including performing system maintenance, displaying personalized content (such as credit ratings), performing company analysis, or sending mailings for us from our advertisers. These parties are all subject to confidentiality agreements that restrict their use and disclosure of information they obtain through their relationship with Company Director Check. 
  * Company Director Check and its partner websites such as Director Check may share information for site administration or order fulfillment, and to notify you of products and services that may interest you. 

### What Kind of Security Measures Do We Take to Protect Your Information From Accidental Loss or Disclosure?

Company Director Check is committed to protecting your personal information. We store information you provide us on our secure servers. Further, the information you provide when making a purchase is encrypted with SSL technology.

Only you have access to these password-protected areas. Do not share your passwords with anyone. Company Director Check will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. If you are using a computer to which others have access, such as one in a computer lab, Internet cafe, or public library, always remember to log out and close your browser window when leaving our site.

### Will Company Director Check Use Your Information for Direct Mailings?

If you register with Company Director Check or sign up for or buy any of our products or services, we will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services that we believe may interest you.

If you do not want to receive such offers and mailings, let us know on our contact page, or you may send a letter to Company Director Check, 11 Church Road, Great Bookham, Surrey, KT23 3PB. We'll remove your name from our lists as soon as we can. Another way is to simply to click the "unsubscribe" link found in every one of our email messages.

Please note: If you purchase products or services from us, or if you register for an account with us, we may contact you to confirm your purchase, subscription, or registration, or to provide you with information about its terms or features. You may wish to keep these transactional or relationship emails, to help you use our products and services.

### How Will You Know Whether Company Director Check's Privacy Policy Has Changed?

We may change this Privacy Statement at any time, but we will give notice of any material change (or any notices that we are required to give you) on our websites.

|   
---|---|---
